Hello to you too.
(Leonard:)How was rock climbing?
(Kripke:)He passed out.
Just hung there like a big salami.
Eh, eh, eh. That's where I sit.
(Kripke:)Ooh, you have a special spot.
What kind of wacko are you?
(Howard:)How much time you got?
You want some Chinese food?
Terrific. Got any dental floss?
(Leonard:)In the bathroom.
(Kripke:)Be right back.
I gotta floss the lndian food out of my teeth
if I'm gonna eat Chinese.
(Penny:)Sheldon, are you okay?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. I pass out all the time.
(Sheldon:)But it was worth it. I've made substantial
progress in bonding with Kripke...
(Sheldon:)...which brings me
to an awkward moment.
- What's that?
- Maintaining five friendships...
(Sheldon:)...promises to be a Herculean task.
(Sheldon:)So I'm going to have
to let one of you go.
(Howard:)Me, me, let it be me.